National Railroad Adjustment Board Case Files 5837
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Railroad Adjustment Board Case Files
1945-1976
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Railroad Adjustment Board
5837
69 cubic feet
69 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5713647
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 21, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6356 PUBS: National Railroad Adjustment Board, First Division, Awards Publications
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Railroads -- United States -- Employees; Arbitration and award -- United States; United States. National Railroad Adjustment Board
5713647
- N.R.A.B. First Division Award Books Volumes 1 to 27 (Box 1)
  - Docket No. 474. Award No. 480. Railroad Yardmasters of America v. TRRA of St. Louis., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Docket No. 475. Award No. 481. Kentucky and Indiana Terminal Railroad Company vs. RYA, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Docket No. 476. Award No. 482. Union Pacific Railroad., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Docket No. 477. Award No. 483. Union Pacific Railroad. Pocatello, Idaho., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Docket No. 479. Award No. 484. Union Pacific Railroad. East Portland and Terminal No. 4., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Docket No. 480. Award No. 485. Union Pacific Railroad. Las Vegas, Nevada., 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Docket No. 481. Award No. 486. Union Pacific Railroad. Spokane, Washington., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Docket No. 501. Award No. 494. Chesapeake and Ohio. B.W. Lane. Richmond Division Board of Management., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Docket No. 495. Award No. 497. C.B. and Q. F.F. Gibbons. Sheridan, Wyoming., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Docket No. 496. Award No. 498. C.B. and Q. Railroad. C.G. Yakel. Lincoln, Nebraska., 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Docket No. 497. Award No. 499. C.B. and Q. J.H. Detwiler. Lincoln, Nebraska., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Docket No. 498. Award No. 500. C.B. and Q. W.L. Devian. Omaha, Nebraska., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Docket No. 499. Award No. 501. C.B. and Q. Sick Leave Payments., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Docket No. 499. C.B. and Q. Sick Leave Payments., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Docket No. 500. Award No. 502. Southern Pacific Co. Chevrolet Yard. Oakland, California., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Docket No. 502. Award No. 503. Chesapeake and Ohio. C.P. Meadows and E.H. Rice., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Docket No. 505. Award No. 506. PRR. 2nd Trick, Re-Class. Lincoln Yard, Detroit., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Docket No. 527. Award No. 511. Chicago, West Pullman and Southern. John O'Janovac., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Docket No. 544. Award No. 524. Northern Pacific. M.L. Dixon. Everett, Michigan., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Docket No. 545. Award No. 527. KCT. Yardmasters. Kansas City, Missouri., 1951 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Docket No. 515. Award No. 534. Nashville Terminals. Kayne Avenue. Middle Yard, Nashville, Tennessee. O.G. Maddux., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Docket No. 523. Award No. 536. Union Pacific. O.F. Williams. Denver, Colorado., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Docket No. 530. Award No. 537. C and O. R.E. Powell., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Docket No. 516. Award No. 538. St. Louis and san Francisco. Afton, Oklahoma. First, Second and Third Tricks., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Docket No. 529. Award No. 541. Northern Pacific. Pasco, Washington., 1949-1951 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Docket No. 569. Award No. 544. Ogden Union Railroad and Depot Company. L.O. Gould., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Scope and Contents
    Ogden, Utah.
  - Docket No. 587. Award No. 551. Santa Fe. Barstow, California., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Docket No. 532. Award No. 558. C and O. Ronceverte, West Virginia., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    H.B. Williams
  - Docket No. 540. Award No. 559. C and O. Marina, Ohio., 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Docket No. 566. Award No.563. D.L. and W. Railroad. W.D. Maylan. Buffalo, New York., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Docket No. 533. Award No. 565. PRR. O.H. Williams. Sandusky, Ohio., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Docket No. 534. Award No. 566. PRR. J.P. Cooper. Vaughn Yard, Reading, Ohio., 1951 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Docket No. 535. Award No. 567. PRR. W.R. Chatman, J.P. Cooper, J.C. Donahue., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- N.R.A.B. First Division Award Books Volumes 28 to 53 (Box 2)
  - Docket No. 364. Award No. 367. Pennsylvania Railroad. Elm Street, Erie, Pennsylvania., 1946 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Docket No. 383. Award No. 372. R.E. Powell, C and O., 1947 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Docket No. 384. Award No. 391. Chicago Great Western. H. Rush., 1947 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Docket No. 394. Award No. 395. Chicago, Burlington and Quincy. L.M. Wilson., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Docket No. 392. Award No. 405. Kenova Yard, West Virginia. C and O., 1947 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Docket No. 393. Award No. 406. Russell Car Shop, Russell, New York. C and O., 1947 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Docket No. 404. Award No. 413. Pennsylvania Railroad. Grand Rapids, Michigan., 1945 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Docket No. 412. Award No. 416. J.E. Murray, C and O., 1947 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Docket No. 413. Award No. 417. W.C. Stinson., 1947 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Docket No. 414. Award No. 418. Murray, Bartlett and Burnett., 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Docket No. 415. Award No. 419. Peach Creek, West Virginia., 1947 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Docket No. 416. Award No. 420. Akron Junction., 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Docket No. 427. Award No. 422. Pennsylvania Railroad. Alabama Ship Yard and Ebenezer North End., 1947 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Docket No. 432. Award No. 423. TRRA. B.K. Crass., 1947 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Docket No. 424. Award No. 425. Nashville Terminal. B7 Castleman., 1947 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Docket No. 441. Award No. 427. Pennsylvania Railroad. T.R. Aljoe., 1947 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Docket No. 435. Award No. 431. Ogden Union Railroad and Depot Company. J.R. Morris, J.E. Newey., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Docket No. 428. Award No. 436. Pennsylvania Railroad. Burrows Lot Yard., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Docket No. 430. Award No. 438. Pennsylvania Railroad. C.N. Parkinson., 1958 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Docket No. 431. Award No. 439. Long Island Railroad. Sidney Young., 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Docket No. 450. Award No. 440. C, B, and Q. Sick Leave Payments., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Docket No. 439. Award No. 443. Southern Pacific Company. C.V. Westbrook., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Docket No. 440. Award No. 444. Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul. E. Dorsch., 1951 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Docket No. 442. Award No. 445. Long Island Railroad Company. Third Trick. Jamaica Storage Yard., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Docket No. 443. Award No. 446. Long Island Railroad Co. Second Trick. Babylon, New York., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Docket No. 454. Award No. 456. Nashville Terminals. H.A. Carrier., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Docket No. 456. Award No. 458. Seaboard Air Line. A.G. Hudson., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Docket No. 478. Award No. 464. Union Pacific. W.A. Stever. Reith, Oregon., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Docket No. 485. Award No. 467. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co. East End, Richmond, California., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Santa Fe. Richmond, California., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Docket No. 463. Award No. 474. Pennsylvania Railroad, Lincoln Yard, Detroit., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Docket No. 471. Award No. 478. Southern Pacific. G.E. De Waide., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Docket No. 472. Award No. 479. C and O., 1950 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Docket No. 445. Award No. 448. Pennsylvania Railroad. 300 and 400 Yard, Indianapolis, Indiana., 1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Docket No. 448. Award No. 451. Pennsylvania Railroad. Enolco Car Shop., 1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Docket No. 451. Award No. 454. Northern Pacific Company. F.T. Corrigan., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - The Pennsylvania Railroad, Indianapolis Division. Documents., 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- N.R.A.B. First Division Award Books Volumes 54 to 77 (Box 3)
  - Award No. 1542. Docket No. 1620. Railroad Yardmasters of America. Yardmaster H.L. Saskie., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Award No. 1543. Docket No. 1621. Railroad Yardmasters of America. Phoenix, Arizona., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Award No. 1544. Docket No. 1628. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe vs. RYA., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Award No. 1545. Docket No. 1629. RYA vs. Lehigh Valley Railroad Company., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Award No. 1546. Docket No. 1630. RYA vs. Lehigh Valley Railroad., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Award No. 1547. Docket No. 1631. RYA vs. Lehigh Valley Railroad., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Award No. 1548. Docket No. 1632. RYA vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Award No. 1552. Docket No. 1581. RYA and Lehigh Valley Railroad., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Award No. 1559. Docket No. 1656. RYA vs. Florida East Coast Railway Co., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Award No. 1562. Docket No. 1672. RYA vs. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad Co., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Award No. 1563. Docket No. 1676. RYA vs. Houston Belt and Terminal Railway Co., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Award No. 1564. Docket No. 1537. RYA vs. Chicago River and Indiana Railroad Company., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Award No. 1565. Docket No. 1623. RYA vs. Northern Pacific Railway Co., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Award No. 1566. Docket No. 1654. RYA vs. Houston Belt and Terminal Railway Company., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Award No. 1567. Docket No. 1655. RYA vs. Florida East Coast Railway Co., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Award No. 1568. Docket No. 1657. RYA vs. Houston Belt and Terminal Railway Co., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Award No. 1570. Docket No. 1704. RYA vs. Missouri Pacific Railroad Company., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Award No. 1571. Docket No. 1707. RYA vs. Lehigh Valley Railroad Co., 1962 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Award No. 1572. Docket No. 1708. RYA vs. Lehigh Valley Railroad Co. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Award No. 1573. Docket No. 1709. RYA vs. Lehigh Valley Railroad Co., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Award No. 1574. Docket No. 1451. RYA vs. Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad Co., 1962 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Award No. 1575. Docket No. 1482. Missouri-Kansas-Texas Railroad Company of Texas., 1962 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Award No. 1579. Docket No. 1500. Missouri-Kansas-Texas of Texas vs. RYA, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Award No. 1580. Docket No. 1502. RYA vs. The Chicago River and Indiana Railroad Co., 1960 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Award No. 1596. Docket No. 1540. RYA vs. Lehigh Valley Railroad Co., 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Award No. 1597. Docket No. 1541. RYA vs. Lehigh Valley Railroad Co., 1962 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Award No. 1598. Docket No. 1542. RYA vs. Lehigh Valley Railroad Co., 1962 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Award No. 1599. Docket No. 1543. RYA vs. Lehigh Valley Railroad., 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Award No. 1602. Docket No. 1550. RYA vs. Houston Belt and Terminal Railway Co., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Award No. 1603. Docket No. 1551. RYA vs. Missouri Pacific Railroad Co., 1962 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- N.R.A.B. First Division Award Books Volumes 78 to 102 (Box 4)
  - Award No. 1440. Docket No. 1432. Chicago and Northwestern., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Award No. 1446. Docket No. 1460. Chicago and Northwestern. Thanksgiving Holiday Claims., 1959-1962 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Award No. 1447. Docket No. 1461.Chicago and Northwestern. Christmas Holiday Claim., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Award No. 1448. Docket No. 1462. Chicago and Northwestern. Holiday Claim., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Award No. 1451. Docket No. 1499. RYA vs. Southern Railway Co., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Award No. 1458. Docket No. 1508. Missouri-Pacific vs. RYA., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Award No. 1460. Docket No. 1516. Chicago and Northwestern vs. RYA., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Award No. 1462. Docket No. 1474. Grand Trunk Western Railroad Co., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Award No. 1463. Docket No. 1481. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Award No. 1494. Docket No. 1485. RYA vs. Missouri-Pacific Railroad Co., 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Award No. 1495. Docket No. 1486. RYA vs. Missouri-Pacific Railroad Co., 1961 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Award No. 1498. Docket No. 1569. RYA vs. New York, Chicago and St. Louis Railroad Co., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Award No. 1499. Docket No. 1407. RYA vs. B and O., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Award No. 1506. Docket No. 1490. Norfolk Southern Railway Co., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Award No. 1508. Docket No. 1495. RYA vs. DI and W., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Award No. 1511. Docket No. 1520. RYA vs. DL and W., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Award No. 1514. Docket No. 1576. RYA vs. The Texas and Pacific Railroad Co., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Award No. 1516. Docket No. 1583. RYA vs. Minnesota Transfer Railroad Co., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Award No. 1517. Docket No. 1584. RYA vs. Minnesota Transfer Railroad Co., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Award No. 1518. Docket No. 1587. RYA vs. St. Louis-San Francisco Railway Co., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Award No. 1519. Docket No. 1588. RYA vs. St. Louis - San Francisco Railway Co., 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Award No. 1520. Docket No. 1589. RYA vs. St. Louis - San Francisco Railway Co., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Award No. 1521. Docket No. 1590. RYA vs. St. Louis-San Francisco Railway Co., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Award No. 1524. Docket No. 1599. RYA vs. New York, Chicago and St. Louis Railroad Co., 1961 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Award No. 1525. Docket No. 1604. RYA vs. St. Louis - San Francisco Railway Co., 1961 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Award No. 1527. Docket No. 1606. RYA vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co., 1961 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Award No. 1528. Docket No. 1607. RYA vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co., 1961 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Award No. 1529. Docket No. 1539. RYA vs. Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad Co., 1961 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Award No. 1533. Docket No. 1610. RYA vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co., 1961 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Award No. 1534. Docket No. 1611. RYA vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co., 1961 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Award No. 1535. Docket No. 1612. RYA vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co., 1961 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Award No. 1536. Docket No. 1613. RYA vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co., 1961 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Award No. 1537. Docket No. 1614. RYA vs. Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railway Co., 1961 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Award No. 1538. Docket No. 1615. RYA vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co., 1961 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Award No. 1539. Docket No. 1616. RYA vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co., 1961 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Award No. 1540. Docket No. 1617. RYA vs. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co., 1961 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- N.R.A.B. First Division Award Books Volumes 103 to 124 (Box 5)
  - Docket No. 627. Award No. 644. Ogden Union Railway and Depot. Ogden, Utah., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Docket No. 664. Award No. 645. TRRA. East Bound Yard. East St. Louis, Illinois., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Docket No. 665. Award No. 646. TRRA. 23rd Street Yard, St. Louis, Missouri., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Docket No. 624. Award No. 642. The Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad Co. Scranton, PA., 1954 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Docket No. 626. Award No. 643. Ogden Union Railroad and Depot. Ogden, Utah., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Docket No. 618. Award No. 636. Seaboard Air Line Railroad Co. Savannah, Georgia., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Docket No. 621. Award No. 639. Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad Co. Michigan Ave Yard, Buffalo, NY., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Docket No. 622. Award No. 640. Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad Co. Taylor Yard, Scranton, Pennsylvania., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Docket No. 623. Award No. 641. Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad Co. Kingston, Pennsylvania., 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Docket No. 666. Award No. 647. TRRA. South Hump and Bridge Junction. East St. Louis, Illinois., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Docket No. 635. Award No. 648. Florida East Coast. Bowden, Florida., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Docket No. 636. Award No. 649. C,B, and Q., 1949 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Docket No. 637. Award No. 650. C,B, and Q. Casper, Wyoming., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Docket No. 638. Award No. 651. C, B and Q. North La Crosse, Wisconsin., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Docket No. 643. Award No. 655. Northern Pacific. Grove Yard, Minnesota., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Docket No. 645. Award No. 657. Ogden Union Railway and Depot Co. Ogden, Utah., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Docket No. 646. Award No. 658. Wabash Railroad. Mexico, Indiana., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Docket No. 653. Award No. 661. Southern Pacific Railroad. El Paso, Texas., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Docket No. 683. Award No. 665. C, B, and Q. C.C. Carder., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Docket No. 684. Award No. 666. C, B, and Q., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Docket No. 662. Award No. 668. Milwaukee Railroad. Chicago, Illinois., 1949-1955 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Docket No. 667. Award No. 670. Pennsylvania Railroad., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Docket No. 668. Award No. 671. Pennsylvania Railroad., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Docket No. 670. Award No. 672. Southern Pacific Railroad. Portland, Oregon., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Docket No. 671. Award No. 673. Minneapolis, St. Paul and St. Ste Marie. Minneapolis, Minnesota., 1952 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Docket No. 675. Award No. 676. Pennsylvania Railroad. Sandusky Hump., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Docket No. 676. Award No. 677. Pennsylvania Railroad., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Docket No. 677. Award No. 678. Pennsylvania Railroad., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Docket No. 680. Award No. 685. C and O. Marion, Ohio., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Docket No. 685. Award No. 686. Pennsylvania Railroad. Sandusky, Ohio., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Docket No. 695. Award No. 693. Southern Pacific. San Jose Yard, California., 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Docket No. 715. Award No. 698. Southern Pacific, Chevrolet Plant., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- N.R.A.B. First Division Award Books Volumes 125 to 148 (Box 6)
  - Award No. 980. Docket No. 982. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. L.J. Boyer., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Award No. 982. Docket No. 969. St. Louis-San Francisco Railway Co. Vacation Claim., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Award No. 983. Docket No. 970. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad. Williams Claim., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Award No. 984. Docket No. 974. Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad. Vacation Pay., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Award No. 985. Docket No. 977. Union Pacific Railroad Co. Reinstatement., 1955 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Award No. 986. Docket No. 979. Louisiana and Arkansas Railway Co. Vaughn Claim., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Award No. 987. Docket No. 983. Baltimore and Ohio Railway Co., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Award No. 988. Docket No. 984. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Award No. 989. Docket No. 985. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. Sears Claim., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Award No. 992. Docket No. 981. New York, Chicago and St. Louis. Rest Day Claims., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Award No. 995. Docket No. 1019. Union Pacific. Yardmaster Case., 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Award No. 996. Docket No. 1020. Union Pacific. Buckley Claims., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Award No. 1002. Docket No. 1007. Chicago, North Western., 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Award No. 1003. Docket No. 1015. Chicago and North Western Railway Co., 1952-1954 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Award No. 1004. Docket No. 1025. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Award No. 1009. Docket No. 995. TRRA. Rest Day Claim., 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Award No. 1010. Docket No. 996. The Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway. Mock Claim., 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Award No. 1011. Docket No. 997. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Co. Linn Claim., 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Award No. 1012. Docket No. 998. Houston Belt and Terminal Railway Co. Seniority., 1955 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Award No. 1013. Docket No. 1000. Baltimore and Ohio Co., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Award No. 1014. Docket No. 1001. Baltimore and Ohio Railway., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Award No. 1015. Docket No. 1002. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. Bose., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Award No. 1018. Docket No. 1008. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. Claims of Yardmasters., 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Award No. 1023. Docket No. 1011. Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. Murray., 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Award No. 1024. Docket No. 1012. Denver and Rio Grand Western Railway. Time and One Half Investigation., 1955 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Award No. 1025. Docket No. 1016. Stinson, Wilkinson and Dickelman. Time and One Half., 1955 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Award No. 1026. Docket No. 1017. Denver and Rio Grand Western Railroad. Ostrander., 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Award No. 1027. Docket No. 1010. Southern Railway System., 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Award No. 1028. Docket No. 1009. Southern Railway Co. Jordan Case., 1955 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- N.R.A.B. First Division Award Books Volumes 149 to 168 Last Volume (Box 7)
  - Award No. 924. Docket No. 912. Southern Railway. Joey Claim., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Award No. 925. Docket No. 916. Pennsylvania Railroad. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    See Award No. 933
  - Award No. 931. Docket No. 964. New York, Chicago and St. Louis Railroad Co., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Award No. 932. Docket No. 965. New York, Chicago and St. Louis Co., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Award No. 933. Docket No. 916. Pennsylvania Railroad. Blairsville Claim., 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Award No. 936. Docket No. 923. The Virginia Railway Co. Vacation Claim., 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Award No. 942. Docket No. 930. Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad. Omaha Passenger Yard Claims., 1954 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Award No. 943. Docket No. 932. Southern Railway., 1954 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Award No. 945. Docket No. 975. Southern Railway. Jordan Seniority. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Award No. 947. Docket No. 934. Grand Truck Western Railway Co., 1954 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Award No. 948. Docket No. 937. Saint Louis-San Francisco Railroad., 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Award No. 949. Docket No. 938. Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe. Disqualification., 1954-1956 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Award No. 950. Docket No. 939. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad. Request for Job., 1954 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Award No. 951. Docket No. 940. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific. Singleton Claims.\, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Award No. 954. Docket No. 947. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad., 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Award No. 955. Docket No. 948. Pittsburgh and Lake Erie. PW French Case, 15 Claims., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Award No. 957. Docket No. 953. Chicago and Great Western. Vacation., 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Award No. 958. Docket No. 954. Louisiana and Arkansas Railway Co. Vacation Claim., 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Award No. 962. Docket No. 958. Grand Truck Western Railroad Co., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Award No. 965. Docket No. 871. Cleveland Union Terminals Co. Lake Front Jobs., 1952-1953 (Box 7, Folder 20)